<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en">
<title type="text">80's Playground</title>
<generator uri="https://github.com/jekyll/jekyll">Jekyll</generator>
<link rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" href="/feed.xml" />
<link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="" />
<updated>2015-09-10T20:14:59-07:00</updated>
<id>/</id>
<author>
  <name>1980's Staff</name>
  <uri>/</uri>
  
</author>


  

<entry>
  <title type="html"><![CDATA[Saved by the Bell Reviewed Podcast, Reviewed]]></title>
  <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="/sbtb-reviewed/" />
  <id>/sbtb-reviewed</id>
  <published>2015-06-29T00:00:00-07:00</published>
  <updated>2015-06-29T00:00:00-07:00</updated>
  <author>
    <name>1980's Staff</name>
    <uri></uri>
    
  </author>
  <content type="html">
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/sbtb_reviewed.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;SBTB Reviewed Logo&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;intro&quot;&gt;Intro&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I will start off by admitting I have watched every show of the Saved by the Bell Universe. That includes Good Morning Miss Bliss, The College Year(s), TV movies and The New Class. Saved by the Bell Reviewed is a podcast project with four hosts that review every episode of everyone’s favorite 90’s show about a high school clique. I witnessed the launch of the project at the end of Ryan Alexander-Tanner’s run of his Full House Reviewed Blog. Alexander-Tanner wanted to explore the review genre in a podcast format and recruited some of his internet and real-life friend to sign on.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Fast forward to not too long ago where I ran into the original artwork I bought for the Full House Reviewed blog’s banner and it sparked my curiosity for what Ryan was up to and started downloading episodes on tumbolor, ahem, I mean tumblr in their episode archive. I am still a little behind, being somewhere in Season 3 where they are reviewing the Wicked Stepbrother Part II episode. The timing of listening to the show was actually pretty good since I was going through some stressful times and it helped to take my mind off things by listening to four people converse about one of my favorite shows. There are not many podcasts in this space, however, one notable show I have listened to a couple episodes is called “Go Bayside!”, which has a completely different format.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;the-format&quot;&gt;The Format&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There are four hosts, the self proclaimed “Aluminum Four” that rotate as a main host, which release a new episode every Monday. Two hosts are located in the Portland area, and the other two hosts are located in Minnesota.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The team decided to review the show in the order established by IMDB, which closely follows the air date, which is very confusingly out of order from the production codes. The podcast usually starts off with a couple witty or shocking clips from within. Then comes on a rocking opening song that is a loose take on the show’s theme song with original lyrics written by co-host Carolyn Main. The main co-host will summarize a scene or action often coloring it with their own flavor and the other hosts will respond with their own take or stories of how they related to the scene as a kid.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Pretty much every bit of dialog, scheming, clothing choice, background character, plot, and inconsistency, will be covered in the typical hour and a half long session. The review is rounded up with a “lessons learned” segment followed by the podcast’s theme song and sometimes some bonus content, such as the Perfect Strangers theme song or the parody SbtB theme song in a porno they found.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;review&quot;&gt;Review&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I should mention I am not too familiar with the podcast genre, so listening to one I figure it a bit like a radio show. In general, like this review, I think the podcast is a fairly niche project that is intended to have fun in the creative process, while also sharing something with a greater audience. It is not exactly a straightforward interview/discussion style of podcast, it is more of a group conversation. Along with the discussion, some additional creativity is added to the podcast, either at the beginning, end or between through editing, sound manipulation, creation of songs or inclusion of relevant songs into the audio. I think you have to be a fairly hardcore fan of the show and be familiar with the episodes in order to appreciate the content, along with being open to hearing anything, along with raunchy jokes and references. A significant part of reviewing SbtB is evaluating the absence of something, either continuity, logic, relation, interaction and requires deep philosophical grounding in order not to lose oneself in the madness.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The production values for the podcast have paralleled the SbtB show’s progression. The TV show in its earlier episodes felt a little rough and the video quality not quite as crisp or vivid. The first season of the podcast is also rough around the edges where the audio quality and levels can make the podcast fairly difficult to listen to especially if you are listening while in a car. The four hosts seem to be feeling each other out a bit in this season of the podcast. In the second season, new audio gear helps make the sound more clear and consistent, and the hosts are a bit more comfortable, and their roles a little more defined, much like how Zack Morris and AC Slater became frenemies. And in the third season, they seem to really be hitting their stride starting the season out with a strong guest appearance.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The fact there are four hosts may make the podcast a little challenging to listen to and sometimes can be confusing to discern who is speaking on the mid-west end. I find myself mostly listening to it when I am not doing anything that requires logical thought or else I will miss out on the dense content of the show and have to back up to catch why they are talking about someone’s balls. Each host brings something different to the table. Ryan is a big fan of the show, who wrote one of my favorite pieces (&lt;a href=&quot;https://therealfullhousereviewed.wordpress.com/2012/02/08/half-time-show-top-10-saved-by-the-bell-background-characters/&quot;&gt;Top 10 Saved By the Bell Background Characters&lt;/a&gt;) about the show in his Full House Reviewed blog. His friend Carolyn Main, did not really watch the show in her youth and comes from the perspective of a non-fan of the show. Carolyn often will point out that she did not watch it and Ryan will acknowledge that she is cooler for it. Both Ryan and Carolyn are cartoonists/illustrators and are part of the Portland comedy scene.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Austin Gortin met Ryan as a commenter on the Full House Reviewed show (as Teebore) and recruited his long-time friend David Bitzenhofer to host along with him, both hosting from the mid-west. In one notable show David hosted as the main host, he was completely drunk around the Thanksgiving holiday and he had to re-edit responses he made later on, which was hilarious and interesting. Carolyn has a distinctive and creative editing style, where she will insert sound bites from the show and even manipulate them with audio effects. The latest episode I heard was Wicked Step Brother Part II and she did a parody of the Brady Bunch song with lyrics based on the plot of that episode.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The podcast is highly reviewed on iTunes with almost a 5 star rating (21 ratings). One iTunes reviewer of their podcast called-out Carolyn for being crude and graphic for mentioning bodily fluids all the time, which was addressed in one of their shows. It seems since then, the references had declined. Some really interesting guests appearances arrived from time to time some of which had never seen the show before they watched it for the review. One interesting guest I will single out here is Bill Ayers, a former professor and someone totally out of the SbtB demographic, who has a close relationship with Ryan, but &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Bill_Ayers_2008_presidential_election_controversy&quot;&gt;apparently not with Barak Obama&lt;/a&gt;. But unfortunately, much like the TV show, the guests usually just make a one time appearance and are never heard from or referenced again.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I also cannot forget the guest interview by Ryan of actor Henry Brown, who played Lisa Turtle’s dad for one episode. It was a funny interview and had a few insights into the behind the scenes and intents of the creators, such as the fact that the intent of bringing him on was to have him be a somewhat recurring character. Ryan hilariously asks him if his role on Saved by the Bell was the highlight of his career. Sometimes the show can meander on for a while, but the main host will usually move things along and the discussion maintains a fairly organic feel. The part I enjoy the most about the experience is it is like listening in on a group of friends chatting about the show. It is interesting to hear what other people thought of it compared to my own thoughts of the show and conversations I have had while watching it with Tangerine. The show cements the fact that pretty much everyone hates Screech (played by now infamouse Dustin Diamond).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The podcast has developed some vocabulary for the show, which I wonder if it will carry on into the general lexicon for the show. The main protagonists of the show are labeled the “Golden Six” referring to how every story revolves around these characters with all the other students in the background are relegated to watching the action, powerless to do anything meaningful and struggling to be noticed through their unique style, expressions and voices. Another standout phrase is “pink-rimmed fantasy” referring to the screen overlay used to denote a fantasy sequence in the TV show. For some reason “J-O’ed” also sticks out in my mind as a frequent phrase, however, it is not particularly specific to the SbtB show. I will also note, Carloyn Main has some unique pronunciations for major social media outlets.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I would encourage any hardcore fan to check out the poscast and see if they would be otherwise missing out on the conversations. Give the theme song a listen to below and you can also find more info on the show’s hosts.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;theme-song&quot;&gt;Theme Song&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;iframe width=&quot;100%&quot; height=&quot;450&quot; scrolling=&quot;no&quot; frameborder=&quot;no&quot; src=&quot;https://w.soundcloud.com/player/?url=https%3A//api.soundcloud.com/tracks/146783466&amp;amp;auto_play=false&amp;amp;hide_related=false&amp;amp;show_comments=true&amp;amp;show_user=true&amp;amp;show_reposts=false&amp;amp;visual=true&quot;&gt;  &lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;theme-song-lyrics&quot;&gt;Theme Song Lyrics&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;When I’m torrenting old recordings, 
the internet sends me a warning and 
I dont think it will download in time. 
By the time I’ve watched the show, 
it’s half past time to go. 
Chugging one more sip to make this show sit right&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p&gt;It’s alright cus its saved by the… 
just alright cus it’s Saved by the Bell&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p&gt;Why do I watch this show 
and where did the 90’s go. 
Bayside High is run by Zack, 
let’s chill out at the Max. 
Giving Belding panic attacks and 
eating all rad snacks. 
As I lay awake at night, am I wasting my life?&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p&gt;Its alright, cuz it’s saved by the 
just all right I’m in hell, 
lets watch Saved By The Bell.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;where-to-find-the-podcast&quot;&gt;Where to Find the Podcast&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Tumblr: [http://www.sbtbreviewed.com/]&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sticher: [http://www.stitcher.com/podcast/austin-gorton/saved-by-the-bell-reviewed]&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;iTunes: [https://itunes.apple.com/us/podcast/saved-by-the-bell-reviewed/id889658279?mt=2]&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;show-hosts&quot;&gt;Show Hosts&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;table&gt;
  &lt;thead&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;th&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/ryan_alexander-tanner.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Ryan Alexander-Tanner&quot; /&gt;&lt;/th&gt;
      &lt;th&gt;Ryan Alexander-Tanner&lt;/th&gt;
      &lt;th&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://ohyesverynice.com&quot;&gt;ohyesverynice.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/th&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;th&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/david_bitzenhofer.png&quot; alt=&quot;David Bitzenhofer&quot; /&gt;&lt;/th&gt;
      &lt;th&gt;David Bitzenhofer&lt;/th&gt;
      &lt;th&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.therealgentlemenofleisure.com&quot;&gt;therealgentlemenofleisure.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/th&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;th&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/austin_gorton.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Austin Gorton&quot; /&gt;&lt;/th&gt;
      &lt;th&gt;Austin “Teebore” Gortin&lt;/th&gt;
      &lt;th&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://soundonsight.org&quot;&gt;soundonsight.org&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/th&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;th&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/carolyn_main.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Carolyn Main&quot; /&gt;&lt;/th&gt;
      &lt;th&gt;Carolyn Main&lt;/th&gt;
      &lt;th&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://carolynmain.com&quot;&gt;carolynmain.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/th&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/thead&gt;
  &lt;tbody&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt; &lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt; &lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt; &lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;update&quot;&gt;Update&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The team has an Indiegogo campain to try to help raise funds for the costs to run the show, go check it out for some cool items such as trading cards! [https://www.indiegogo.com/projects/saved-by-the-bell-reviewed#/story]&lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;/sbtb-reviewed/&quot;&gt;Saved by the Bell Reviewed Podcast, Reviewed&lt;/a&gt; was originally published by 1980's Staff at &lt;a href=&quot;&quot;&gt;80's Playground&lt;/a&gt; on June 29, 2015.&lt;/p&gt;
  </content>
</entry>


  

<entry>
  <title type="html"><![CDATA[Saved by the Bell Reviewed Podcast, Reviewed]]></title>
  <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="/sbtb-draft-post/" />
  <id>/sbtb-draft-post</id>
  <published>2015-06-29T00:00:00-07:00</published>
  <updated>2015-06-29T00:00:00-07:00</updated>
  <author>
    <name>1980's Staff</name>
    <uri></uri>
    
  </author>
  <content type="html">
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/sbtb_reviewed.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;SBTB Reviewed Logo&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;intro&quot;&gt;Intro&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I will start off by admitting I have watched every show of the Saved by the Bell Universe. That includes Good Morning Miss Bliss, The College Year(s), TV movies and The New Class. Saved by the Bell Reviewed is a podcast project with four hosts that review every episode of everyone’s favorite 90’s show about a high school clique. I witnessed the launch of the project at the end of Ryan Alexander-Tanner’s run of his Full House Reviewed Blog. Alexander-Tanner wanted to explore the review genre in a podcast format and recruited some of his internet and real-life friend to sign on.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Fast forward to not too long ago where I ran into the original artwork I bought for the Full House Reviewed blog and it sparked my curiosity for what Ryan was up to and started downloading episodes on tumbolor, ahem, I mean tumblr in their episode archive. I am still a little behind, being somewhere in Season 3 where they are reviewing the Wicked Stepbrother Part II episode. The timing of listening to the show was actually pretty good since I was going through some stressful times and it helped to take my mind off things by listening to four people converse about one of my favorite shows. There are not many podcasts in this space, however, one notable show I have listened to a couple episodes is called “Go Bayside!”, which has a completely different format.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;the-format&quot;&gt;The Format&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There are four hosts, the self proclaimed “Aluminum Four” that rotate as a main host, which release a new episode every Monday. Two hosts are located in the Portland area, and the other two hosts are located in Minnesota.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The team decided to review the show in the order established by IMDB, which closely follows the air date, which is very confusingly out of order from the production codes. The podcast usually starts off with a couple witty or shocking clips from within. Then comes on a rocking opening song that is a loose take on the show’s theme song with original lyrics written by co-host Carolyn Main. The main co-host will summarize a scene or action often coloring it with their own flavor and the other hosts will respond with their own take or stories of how they related to the scene as a kid.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Pretty much every bit of dialog, scheming, clothing choice, background character, plot, and inconsistency, will be covered in the typical hour and a half long session. The review is rounded up with a “lessons learned” segment followed by the podcast’s theme song and sometimes some bonus content, such as the Perfect Strangers theme song or the parody SbtB theme song in a porno they found.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;review&quot;&gt;Review&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I should mention I am not too familiar with the podcast genre, so listening to one I figure it a bit like a radio show. In general, like this review, I think the podcast is a fairly niche project that is intended to have fun in the creative process, while also sharing something with a greater audience. It is not exactly a straightforward interview/discussion style of podcast, it is more of a group conversation. Along with the discussion, some additional creativity is added to the podcast, either at the beginning, end or between through editing, sound manipulation, creation of songs or inclusion of relevant songs into the audio. I think you have to be a fairly hardcore fan of the show and be familiar with the episodes in order to appreciate the content, along with being open to hearing anything, along with raunchy jokes and references. A significant part of reviewing SbtB is evaluating the absence of something, either continuity, logic, relation, interaction and requires deep philosophical grounding in order not to lose oneself in the madness.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The production values for the podcast have paralleled the SbtB show’s progression. The TV show in its earlier episodes felt a little rough and the video quality not quite as crisp or vivid. The first season of the podcast is also rough around the edges where the audio quality and levels can make the podcast fairly difficult to listen to especially if you are listening while in a car. The four hosts seem to be feeling each other out a bit in this season of the podcast. In the second season, new audio gear helps make the sound more clear and consistent, and the hosts are a bit more comfortable, and their roles a little more defined, much like how Zack Morris and AC Slater became frenemies. And in the third season, they seem to really be hitting their stride starting the season out with a strong guest appearance.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The fact there are four hosts may make the podcast a little challenging to listen to and sometimes can be confusing to discern who is speaking on the mid-west end. I find myself mostly listening to it when I am not doing anything that requires logical thought or else I will miss out on the dense content of the show and have to back up to catch why they are talking about someone’s balls. Each host brings something different to the table. Ryan is a big fan of the show, who wrote one of my favorite pieces (&lt;a href=&quot;https://therealfullhousereviewed.wordpress.com/2012/02/08/half-time-show-top-10-saved-by-the-bell-background-characters/&quot;&gt;Top 10 Saved By the Bell Background Characters&lt;/a&gt;) about the show in his Full House Reviewed blog. His friend Carolyn Main, did not really watch the show in her youth and comes from the perspective of a non-fan of the show. Carolyn often will point out that she did not watch it and Ryan will acknowledge that she is cooler for it. Both Ryan and Carolyn are cartoonists/illustrators and are part of the Portland comedy scene.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Austin Gortin met Ryan as a commenter on the Full House Reviewed show (as Teebore) and recruited his long-time friend David Bitzenhofer to host along with him, both hosting from the mid-west. In one notable show David hosted as the main host, he was completely drunk around the Thanksgiving holiday and he had to re-edit responses he made later on, which was hilarious and interesting. Carolyn has a distinctive and creative editing style, where she will insert sound bites from the show and even manipulate them with audio effects. The latest episode I heard was Wicked Step Brother Part II and she did a parody of the Brady Bunch song with lyrics based on the plot of that episode.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The podcast is highly reviewed on iTunes with almost a 5 star rating (21 ratings). One iTunes reviewer of their podcast called-out Carolyn for being crude and graphic for mentioning bodily fluids all the time, which was addressed in one of their shows. It seems since then, the references had declined. Some really interesting guests appearances arrived from time to time some of which had never seen the show before they watched it for the review. One interesting guest I will single out here is Bill Ayers, a former professor and someone totally out of the SbtB demographic, who has a close relationship with Ryan, but &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Bill_Ayers_2008_presidential_election_controversy&quot;&gt;apparently not with Barak Obama&lt;/a&gt;. But unfortunately, much like the TV show, the guests usually just make a one time appearance and are never heard from or referenced again.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I also cannot forget the guest interview by Ryan of actor Henry Brown, who played Lisa Turtle’s dad for one episode. It was a funny interview and had a few insights into the behind the scenes and intents of the creators, such as the fact that the intent of bringing him on was to have him be a somewhat recurring character. Ryan hilariously asks him if his role on Saved by the Bell was the highlight of his career. Sometimes the show can meander on for a while, but the main host will usually move things along and the discussion maintains a fairly organic feel. The part I enjoy the most about the experience is it is like listening in on a group of friends chatting about the show. It is interesting to hear what other people thought of it compared to my own thoughts of the show and conversations I have had while watching it with Tangerine.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The podcast has developed some vocabulary for the show, which I wonder if it will carry on into the general lexicon for the show. The main protagonists of the show are labeled the “Golden Six” referring to how every story revolves around these characters with all the other students in the background are relegated to watching the action, powerless to do anything meaningful and struggling to be noticed through their unique style, expressions and voices. Another standout phrase is “pink-rimmed fantasy” referring to the screen overlay used to denote a fantasy sequence in the TV show. For some reason “J-O’ed” also sticks out in my mind as a frequent phrase, however, it is not particularly specific to the SbtB show. I will also note, Carloyn Main has some unique pronunciations for major social media outlets.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I would encourage any hardcore fan to check out the poscast and see if they would be otherwise missing out on the conversations. Give the theme song a listen to below and you can also find more info on the show’s hosts.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;theme-song&quot;&gt;Theme Song&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;iframe width=&quot;100%&quot; height=&quot;450&quot; scrolling=&quot;no&quot; frameborder=&quot;no&quot; src=&quot;https://w.soundcloud.com/player/?url=https%3A//api.soundcloud.com/tracks/146783466&amp;amp;auto_play=false&amp;amp;hide_related=false&amp;amp;show_comments=true&amp;amp;show_user=true&amp;amp;show_reposts=false&amp;amp;visual=true&quot;&gt;  &lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;theme-song-lyrics&quot;&gt;Theme Song Lyrics&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;When I’m torrenting old recordings, 
the internet sends me a warning and 
I dont think it will download in time. 
By the time I’ve watched the show, 
it’s half past time to go. 
Chugging one more sip to make this show sit right&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p&gt;It’s alright cus its saved by the… 
just alright cus it’s Saved by the Bell&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p&gt;Why do I watch this show 
and where did the 90’s go. 
Bayside High is run by Zack, 
let’s chill out at the Max. 
Giving Belding panic attacks and 
eating all rad snacks. 
As I lay awake at night, am I wasting my life?&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p&gt;Its alright, cuz it’s saved by the 
just all right I’m in hell, 
lets watch Saved By The Bell.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;show-hosts&quot;&gt;Show Hosts&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;table&gt;
  &lt;thead&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;th&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/ryan_alexander-tanner.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Ryan Alexander-Tanner&quot; /&gt;&lt;/th&gt;
      &lt;th&gt;Ryan Alexander-Tanner&lt;/th&gt;
      &lt;th&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://ohyesverynice.com&quot;&gt;ohyesverynice.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/th&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;th&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/david_bitzenhofer.png&quot; alt=&quot;David Bitzenhofer&quot; /&gt;&lt;/th&gt;
      &lt;th&gt;David Bitzenhofer&lt;/th&gt;
      &lt;th&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.therealgentlemenofleisure.com&quot;&gt;therealgentlemenofleisure.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/th&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;th&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/austin_gorton.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Austin Gorton&quot; /&gt;&lt;/th&gt;
      &lt;th&gt;Austin “Teebore” Gortin&lt;/th&gt;
      &lt;th&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://soundonsight.org&quot;&gt;soundonsight.org&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/th&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;th&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/carolyn_main.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Carolyn Main&quot; /&gt;&lt;/th&gt;
      &lt;th&gt;Carolyn Main&lt;/th&gt;
      &lt;th&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://carolynmain.com&quot;&gt;carolynmain.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/th&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/thead&gt;
  &lt;tbody&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt; &lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt; &lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt; &lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;


    &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;/sbtb-draft-post/&quot;&gt;Saved by the Bell Reviewed Podcast, Reviewed&lt;/a&gt; was originally published by 1980's Staff at &lt;a href=&quot;&quot;&gt;80's Playground&lt;/a&gt; on June 29, 2015.&lt;/p&gt;
  </content>
</entry>


  

<entry>
  <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fake &quot;The Hundreds&quot; Garbage Pail Kids Card Set]]></title>
  <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="/Travis-Tierno-Fake-The-Hundreds/" />
  <id>/Travis-Tierno-Fake-The-Hundreds</id>
  <published>2015-04-11T10:55:00-07:00</published>
  <updated>2015-04-11T10:55:00-07:00</updated>
  <author>
    <name>1980's Staff</name>
    <uri></uri>
    
  </author>
  <content type="html">
    &lt;p&gt;The 1980s staff has some unfortunate news regarding the “The Hundreds trading card set” that was sold and promoted by Travis Tierno. We have contacted The Hundreds Company and a number of other sources and found out that they never released this set of small (2.5” x 3.5”) trading cards. There are other items released by &lt;a href=&quot;http://thehundreds.com/&quot;&gt;The Hundreds&lt;/a&gt; such as jumbo cards, jumbo wax pack and keychains that were officially licensed by Topps.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://s14.postimg.org/41o86a50h/GPK_1_A.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://s27.postimg.org/9tge331c3/GPK_1_B.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The sale of the cards started with a promo card giveaway made on the Garbage Pail Kids Underground Forum (GPKUG), where Tierno subsequently became a moderator. Every sale from original owners of the small The Hundreds card set and promo card can be traced back to him. Original sets sold in 2013 for $20-30 on the GPKUG while recently sets have sold upwards to $55-65 and higher for non-US buyers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The set was advertised as a limited edition of 50 sets, and Tierno claimed he secured 25 of the 50 for sale. More than 36 sold sets were counted. Layron DeJarnette (an official Topps Artist), who created the original artwork had no prior knowledge of the bootleg set. They do not have no copyright and the quality is not up to typical standards. He has been demodded in most groups and was banned from GPK Underground forum and other groups on Facebook.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://i.imgur.com/uFVFBmE.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;P1 promo card&quot; /&gt;
The P1 promo card (shown here) featuring the original cloud banner is a complete fabrication based on art lifted from the original Adam Bomb card and The Hundreds cherry bomb character painted by DeJarnette.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;email-from-the-hundreds-representative&quot;&gt;Email from The Hundreds Representative&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Unfortunately, we never produced small
cards, we did make 15 large sets though
and about 40 large singles that were also
stickers. The large singles were only for
promo, not for sale. There is a slight
possibility that Topps made the cards, but
we are not too sure, you may reach out to
them for more information. Sorry! Wish we
could have provided more information, I
would recommend reaching out to Topps
for any other questions.&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p&gt;Thank you for your support!&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p&gt;The Hundreds Service&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p&gt;Jasmine Ortega, Customer Service l Sales&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;update&quot;&gt;UPDATE&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There is an extensive thread at the &lt;a href=&quot;http://nonsportupdate.infopop.cc/eve/forums/a/tpc/f/954605353/m/2577004176&quot;&gt;Non-sport Update Forum&lt;/a&gt; where member “David R” asks where the set came from after buying it from Tierno in a Facebook group. Another member “Martian Commander” chimed in claiming he worked for Topps and worked on The Hundreds set with the company also poster there wanting to know where the set came from as well. The inquiry was made almost a year before the fraud was discovered.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It is now known &lt;strong&gt;Adam&lt;/strong&gt; Levine is “Martian Commander” and was in contact with Tierno sometime last year entrusting him with distributing promo cards to the community along with giving him other exclusive goods. Levine had been given a package of &lt;strong&gt;Adam&lt;/strong&gt; Bomb themed goods by Tierno and his friends to secure relations for community group giveaways, but a portion of those items were being sold or traded for by Tierno instead. Levine no longer works for Topps.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;quote-from-adam-levine&quot;&gt;Quote from Adam Levine&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Just became of aware of this. I didn’t have his contact info previously. Wasn’t aware this was such a significant problem until now.&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p&gt;Am dealing with it currently… disappointed to see it was a trusted member of the community.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Continue the discussion here: &lt;!-- ![](http://i.imgur.com/s42yJYu.png) --&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;http://1980s.me/f/1179-fake-hundreds-sets/&quot;&gt;1980s Forums: Fake Hundreds Sets&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sources:
-&lt;a href=&quot;http://nonsportupdate.infopop.cc/eve/forums/a/tpc/f/954605353/m/2577004176&quot;&gt;Non-sport Update&lt;/a&gt;
-&lt;a href=&quot;http://imgur.com/a/U3MUX&quot;&gt;Imgur Gallery&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;/Travis-Tierno-Fake-The-Hundreds/&quot;&gt;Fake &amp;quot;The Hundreds&amp;quot; Garbage Pail Kids Card Set&lt;/a&gt; was originally published by 1980's Staff at &lt;a href=&quot;&quot;&gt;80's Playground&lt;/a&gt; on April 11, 2015.&lt;/p&gt;
  </content>
</entry>


  

<entry>
  <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sample Post]]></title>
  <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="/sample-post/" />
  <id>/sample-post</id>
  <updated>2013-05-31T00:00:00-00:00</updated>
  <published>2011-03-10T00:00:00-08:00</published>
  
  <author>
    <name>1980's Staff</name>
    <uri></uri>
    
  </author>
  <content type="html">
    &lt;section id=&quot;table-of-contents&quot; class=&quot;toc&quot;&gt;
  &lt;header&gt;
    &lt;h3&gt;Overview&lt;/h3&gt;
  &lt;/header&gt;
&lt;div id=&quot;drawer&quot;&gt;
&lt;ul id=&quot;markdown-toc&quot;&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#html-elements&quot; id=&quot;markdown-toc-html-elements&quot;&gt;HTML Elements&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#heading-1&quot; id=&quot;markdown-toc-heading-1&quot;&gt;Heading 1&lt;/a&gt;    &lt;ul&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#heading-2&quot; id=&quot;markdown-toc-heading-2&quot;&gt;Heading 2&lt;/a&gt;        &lt;ul&gt;
          &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#heading-3&quot; id=&quot;markdown-toc-heading-3&quot;&gt;Heading 3&lt;/a&gt;            &lt;ul&gt;
              &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#heading-4&quot; id=&quot;markdown-toc-heading-4&quot;&gt;Heading 4&lt;/a&gt;                &lt;ul&gt;
                  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#heading-5&quot; id=&quot;markdown-toc-heading-5&quot;&gt;Heading 5&lt;/a&gt;                    &lt;ul&gt;
                      &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#heading-6&quot; id=&quot;markdown-toc-heading-6&quot;&gt;Heading 6&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
                    &lt;/ul&gt;
                  &lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;/ul&gt;
              &lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;/ul&gt;
          &lt;/li&gt;
          &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#body-text&quot; id=&quot;markdown-toc-body-text&quot;&gt;Body text&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
          &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#blockquotes&quot; id=&quot;markdown-toc-blockquotes&quot;&gt;Blockquotes&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;/ul&gt;
      &lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#list-types&quot; id=&quot;markdown-toc-list-types&quot;&gt;List Types&lt;/a&gt;        &lt;ul&gt;
          &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#ordered-lists&quot; id=&quot;markdown-toc-ordered-lists&quot;&gt;Ordered Lists&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
          &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#unordered-lists&quot; id=&quot;markdown-toc-unordered-lists&quot;&gt;Unordered Lists&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;/ul&gt;
      &lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#tables&quot; id=&quot;markdown-toc-tables&quot;&gt;Tables&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#code-snippets&quot; id=&quot;markdown-toc-code-snippets&quot;&gt;Code Snippets&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#buttons&quot; id=&quot;markdown-toc-buttons&quot;&gt;Buttons&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#notices&quot; id=&quot;markdown-toc-notices&quot;&gt;Notices&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

  &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/section&gt;
&lt;!-- /#table-of-contents --&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;html-elements&quot;&gt;HTML Elements&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Below is just about everything you’ll need to style in the theme. Check the source code to see the many embedded elements within paragraphs.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;heading-1&quot;&gt;Heading 1&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;heading-2&quot;&gt;Heading 2&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;heading-3&quot;&gt;Heading 3&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;heading-4&quot;&gt;Heading 4&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;h5 id=&quot;heading-5&quot;&gt;Heading 5&lt;/h5&gt;

&lt;h6 id=&quot;heading-6&quot;&gt;Heading 6&lt;/h6&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;body-text&quot;&gt;Body text&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet, test link adipiscing elit. &lt;strong&gt;This is strong&lt;/strong&gt;. Nullam dignissim convallis est. Quisque aliquam.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;image-pull-right&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/3953273590_704e3899d5_m.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Smithsonian Image&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;This is emphasized&lt;/em&gt;. Donec faucibus. Nunc iaculis suscipit dui. 53 = 125. Water is H2O. Nam sit amet sem. Aliquam libero nisi, imperdiet at, tincidunt nec, gravida vehicula, nisl. The New York Times (That’s a citation). Underline.Maecenas ornare tortor. Donec sed tellus eget sapien fringilla nonummy. Mauris a ante. Suspendisse quam sem, consequat at, commodo vitae, feugiat in, nunc. Morbi imperdiet augue quis tellus.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;HTML and CSS are our tools. Mauris a ante. Suspendisse quam sem, consequat at, commodo vitae, feugiat in, nunc. Morbi imperdiet augue quis tellus. Praesent mattis, massa quis luctus fermentum, turpis mi volutpat justo, eu volutpat enim diam eget metus.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;blockquotes&quot;&gt;Blockquotes&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet, test link adipiscing elit. Nullam dignissim convallis est. Quisque aliquam.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;list-types&quot;&gt;List Types&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;ordered-lists&quot;&gt;Ordered Lists&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Item one
    &lt;ol&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;sub item one&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;sub item two&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;sub item three&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ol&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Item two&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;unordered-lists&quot;&gt;Unordered Lists&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Item one&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Item two&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Item three&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;tables&quot;&gt;Tables&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;table rules=&quot;groups&quot;&gt;
  &lt;thead&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;th style=&quot;text-align: left&quot;&gt;Header1&lt;/th&gt;
      &lt;th style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;Header2&lt;/th&gt;
      &lt;th style=&quot;text-align: right&quot;&gt;Header3&lt;/th&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/thead&gt;
  &lt;tbody&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: left&quot;&gt;cell1&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;cell2&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: right&quot;&gt;cell3&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: left&quot;&gt;cell4&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;cell5&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: right&quot;&gt;cell6&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/tbody&gt;
  &lt;tbody&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: left&quot;&gt;cell1&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;cell2&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: right&quot;&gt;cell3&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: left&quot;&gt;cell4&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;cell5&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: right&quot;&gt;cell6&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/tbody&gt;
  &lt;tfoot&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: left&quot;&gt;Foot1&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;Foot2&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: right&quot;&gt;Foot3&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/tfoot&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;code-snippets&quot;&gt;Code Snippets&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code class=&quot;language-css&quot; data-lang=&quot;css&quot;&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;nf&quot;&gt;#container&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;{&lt;/span&gt;
  &lt;span class=&quot;k&quot;&gt;float&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;o&quot;&gt;:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;k&quot;&gt;left&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;;&lt;/span&gt;
  &lt;span class=&quot;k&quot;&gt;margin&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;o&quot;&gt;:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;m&quot;&gt;0&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;m&quot;&gt;-240px&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;m&quot;&gt;0&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;m&quot;&gt;0&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;;&lt;/span&gt;
  &lt;span class=&quot;k&quot;&gt;width&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;o&quot;&gt;:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;m&quot;&gt;100%&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;}&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;buttons&quot;&gt;Buttons&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Make any link standout more when applying the &lt;code&gt;.btn&lt;/code&gt; class.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code class=&quot;language-html&quot; data-lang=&quot;html&quot;&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;nt&quot;&gt;&amp;lt;a&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;na&quot;&gt;href=&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;s&quot;&gt;&amp;quot;#&amp;quot;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;na&quot;&gt;class=&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;s&quot;&gt;&amp;quot;btn btn-success&amp;quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;nt&quot;&gt;&amp;gt;&lt;/span&gt;Success Button&lt;span class=&quot;nt&quot;&gt;&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;div&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#&quot; class=&quot;btn&quot;&gt;Primary Button&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#&quot; class=&quot;btn btn-success&quot;&gt;Success Button&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#&quot; class=&quot;btn btn-warning&quot;&gt;Warning Button&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#&quot; class=&quot;btn btn-danger&quot;&gt;Danger Button&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#&quot; class=&quot;btn btn-info&quot;&gt;Info Button&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;notices&quot;&gt;Notices&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;notice&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Watch out!&lt;/strong&gt; You can also add notices by appending &lt;code&gt;{: .notice}&lt;/code&gt; to a paragraph.&lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;/sample-post/&quot;&gt;Sample Post&lt;/a&gt; was originally published by 1980's Staff at &lt;a href=&quot;&quot;&gt;80's Playground&lt;/a&gt; on March 10, 2011.&lt;/p&gt;
  </content>
</entry>

</feed>
